mylot.com 2012-06-22

# myLot - Privacy Policy

**myLot.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.**

**About myLot Privacy**

This policy explains how myLot treats personal information that myLot collects and receives when an individual becomes a myLot member. Personal information is information that is personally identifiable like your name, address, birth date, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy applies only to myLot and does not apply to the practices of companies that myLot does not own or control or to people that myLot does not employ or manage. In addition, certain myLot associated companies have their own privacy statements which can be viewed by going to their websites. 

**General Information**

myLot collects personal information such as your name, email address, country you reside in, and birth date when you register for our services. myLot may also collect other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. Once you register with myLot and sign in to our services, your personal information will only be available to us and will remain anonymous to other myLot members. 

**Security**

myLot member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. myLot takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on myLot.com, please contact us with your questions or concerns. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosing**

User Profile information such as user id is displayed to myLot members in order to facilitate user interaction in the myLot social networking community. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, myLot allows users to search for other members by user ID, and country of residence. When using myLot Mail, your first name will be displayed. myLot.com displays little personal information in order to keep a safe and secure environment for all myLot.com members. 

From time to time, myLot or a partner of myLot, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstakes, or contest on myLot.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address, home address, and/or answer certain questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply. 

As otherwise described in this privacy statement, myLot will not disclose any personal information to a third party, except if any situation arises and myLot believes disclosure is necessary. The following are exceptions: 

  * myLot will conform to any legal requirements, respond to a subpoena, search warrant or any other legal process received, whether or not a response is required by applicable law 
  * myLot also reserves the right to exchange any personal information to any related companies.
  * myLot will enforce the myLot “Terms of Agreement” to protect our rights; and to protect the safety of members of the public and users of myLot.com 
  * myLot reserves the right to transfer personal information to any successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of myLot or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. 

If you have any concern about your personal information, please feel free to contact us, and we will assist you with any concerns. 

**Communication between Members and Non-members**

**myLot Mail**  
Members  
myLot Mail is used for the purpose of inviting friends to discuss topics of interest in a private and safe environment. When an individual signs up for a myLot account, that member automatically is signed up for myLot Mail. Your user id name will be your myLot Mail address. myLot Mail can only be used within the myLot network. When a member receives a myLot message from another member, the user will need to Allow or Disallow this person from sending future myLot Mail to them. This is how we help to prevent spam. You only get approved mail after the initial contact. Members can easily view and edit their Allow / Disallow list at any time. 

Non-members  
myLot is a closed network, so a member cannot receive emails from traditional email addresses. However, if a myLot member wants to invite an individual with a traditional email address to join myLot, a notification will be sent to that individual’s traditional email address requesting that individual to view your message by joining myLot.com and becoming a myLot member. 

**Discussion Board**  
myLot is a self-regulated social network that encourages myLot members to interact with each other through a discussion board. The myLot discussion board is publicly displayed; meaning members and non-members can view any discussion. Please keep in mind that any private information that you voluntarily post on a discussion board will be displayed. For the safety of all myLot members, we would strongly discourage members from posting any personal information about themselves on a discussion board. myLot would recommend displaying any personal information in myLot Mail for only selected members to view. Following these recommendations will enable myLot to maintain a safe and secure place for members to come and discuss topics of interest. 

**Links**  
myLot is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on myLot. 

**Cookies**

What is a cookie?  
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. 

Choices about Cookies  
You can configure your browser to accept or reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences). In order to take advantage of myLot.com and to use most functions on myLot.com, you must enable cookies from myLot.com. 

Why does myLot.com use cookies?  
myLot uses its own cookies for a number of reasons. myLot uses cookies to store members' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that members are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. myLot can access your information when you "sign in," so that we can provide you with a customized content. myLot can estimate and report our total audience size and traffic and conduct research to improve myLot’s content and services. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

Third Party Advertisers and cookies  
myLot uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this website, other Web sites, and other forms of media in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

**Toolbar for myLot**

Information we collect

  * The myLot Toolbar automatically sends only standard, limited information in order to improve the functions of the myLot Toolbar, which may be retained in myLot’s server logs. It does not send any information about the web pages you visit (e.g., the URL). You do not need to provide any personal information in order to download and use the myLot Toolbar.
  * Your copy of myLot Toolbar includes a unique application number. When you install myLot Toolbar, this number and a message indicating whether the installation succeeded are sent back to myLot. Also, when myLot Toolbar automatically checks to see if a new version is available, the current version number and the unique application number are sent to myLot. The unique application number is required for myLot Toolbar to work and cannot be disabled.
  * Toolbar Features that give you access to other myLot features such as Mozilla Firefox are subject to the separate Privacy Policies, which can be viewed on their websites.
  * The myLot Toolbar contacts our servers periodically to obtain automatic updates to the latest version, or as part of the uninstall process.
  * Except for information sent through Toolbar for use with a separate myLot Account-based service, we do not associate any of the information that Toolbar sends with other personal information about you. However, it is possible that a URL or other page information sent to myLot may itself contain personal information.

Uses 

  * We process your requests in order to operate the myLot Toolbar. 
  * In addition, we use log information about aggregate Toolbar usage to improve the quality of Toolbar and other myLot services.

Information security 

  * Any information sent to myLot will be maintained in accordance with the myLot Privacy Policy

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

myLot reserves the right to make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of the changes that have been made. myLot members are bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.mylot.com/o/contactus.aspx).
